<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="comp">Java Platform technology has entered the lives of the programmers and developers as if it is spoken language in the information technology (IT) world today. No student of information technology has gone untouched and uninfluenced by the Java technology, and such is the influence of the platform. Java, therefore, has assumed immense importance in the information technology world, and offer multitude of choices – APIs, frameworks, standards, etc. for a better application development on multitude of platforms – desktops, Intranets, Extranets, Internet, mobile devices, smart-chips and other emerging newer platforms as well. We, at IIHT, have created the comprehensive Java course, for the exclusive benefit of budding developers and programmers, such as you folks, and divided the content into 3 categories – Core Java, Advanced Java and Web Java. This developer’s guide focuses on Advanced aspects of the Java platform, and this material has been developed for our exclusive use by Altius Inc. This course covers many important topics such as multi-threading, JDBC, JavaBeans framework, Collections Framework, Advanced Object Oriented Concepts, Java Utility libraries, Lambda expressions and functional programming and many other advanced topics. This courseware focuses a lot on the hands-on way of learning advanced aspects of Java, and each chapter includes many small projects, on which students can practice and understand the advanced aspects of the Java platform. I am sure that this guide enormously helps the students in absorbing the concepts that will be useful in the professional career. I wish all the students a happy advanced Java learning  Java Platform technology has entered the lives of the programmers and developers as if it is spoken language in the information technology (IT) world today. No student of information technology has gone untouched and uninfluenced by the Java technology, and such is the influence of the platform. Java, therefore, has assumed immense importance in the information technology world, and offer multitude of choices – APIs, frameworks, standards, etc. for a better application development on multitude of platforms – desktops, Intranets, Extranets, Internet, mobile devices, smart-chips and other emerging newer platforms as well. We, at IIHT, have created the comprehensive Java course, for the exclusive benefit of budding developers and programmers, such as you folks, and divided the content into 3 categories – Core Java, Advanced Java and Web Java. This developer’s guide focuses on Advanced aspects of the Java platform, and this material has been developed for our exclusive use by Altius Inc. This course covers many important topics such as multi-threading, JDBC, JavaBeans framework, Collections Framework, Advanced Object Oriented Concepts, Java Utility libraries, Lambda expressions and functional programming and many other advanced topics.  This courseware focuses a lot on the hands-on way of learning advanced aspects of Java, and each chapter includes many small projects, on which students can practice and understand the advanced aspects of the Java platform. I am sure that this guide enormously helps the students in absorbing the concepts that will be useful in the professional career. I wish all the students a happy advanced Java learning and    Java Platform technology has entered the lives of the programmers and developers as if it is spoken language in the information technology (IT) world today. No student of information technology has gone untouched and uninfluenced by the Java technology, and such is the influence of the platform. Java, therefore, has assumed immense importance in the information technology world, and offer multitude of choices – APIs, frameworks, standards, etc. for a better application development on multitude of platforms – desktops, Intranets, Extranets, Internet, mobile devices, smart-chips and other emerging newer platforms as well. We, at IIHT, have created the comprehensive Java course, for the exclusive benefit of budding developers and programmers, such as you folks, and divided the content into 3 categories – Core Java, Advanced Java and Web Java. This developer’s guide focuses on Advanced aspects of the Java platform, and this material has been developed for our exclusive use by Altius Inc. This course covers many important topics such as multi-threading, JDBC, JavaBeans framework, Collections Framework, Advanced Object Oriented Concepts, Java Utility libraries, Lambda expressions and functional programming and many other advanced topics.  This courseware focuses a lot on the hands-on way of learning advanced aspects of Java, and each chapter includes many small projects, on which students can practice and understand the advanced aspects of the Java platform. I am sure that this guide enormously helps the students in absorbing the concepts that will be useful in the professional career. I wish all the students a happy advanced Java learning and    Java Platform technology has entered the lives of the programmers and developers as if it is spoken language in the information technology (IT) world today. No student of information technology has gone untouched and uninfluenced by the Java technology, and such is the influence of the platform. Java, therefore, has assumed immense importance in the information technology world, and offer multitude of choices – APIs, frameworks, standards, etc. for a better application development on multitude of platforms – desktops, Intranets, Extranets, Internet, mobile devices, smart-chips and other emerging newer platforms as well. We, at IIHT, have created the comprehensive Java course, for the exclusive benefit of budding developers and programmers, such as you folks, and divided the content into 3 categories – Core Java, Advanced Java and Web Java. This developer’s guide focuses on Advanced aspects of the Java platform, and this material has been developed for our exclusive use by Altius Inc. This course covers many important topics such as multi-threading, JDBC, JavaBeans framework, Collections Framework, Advanced Object Oriented Concepts, Java Utility libraries, Lambda expressions and functional programming and many other advanced topics.  This courseware focuses a lot on the hands-on way of learning advanced aspects of Java, and each chapter includes many small projects, on which students can practice and understand the advanced aspects of the Java platform. I am sure that this guide enormously helps the students in absorbing the concepts that will be useful in the professional career. I wish all the students a happy advanced Java learning and    Java Platform technology has entered the lives of the programmers and developers as if it is spoken language in the information technology (IT) world today. No student of information technology has gone untouched and uninfluenced by the Java technology, and such is the influence of the platform. Java, therefore, has assumed immense importance in the information technology world, and offer multitude of choices – APIs, frameworks, standards, etc. for a better application development on multitude of platforms – desktops, Intranets, Extranets, Internet, mobile devices, smart-chips and other emerging newer platforms as well. We, at IIHT, have created the comprehensive Java course, for the exclusive benefit of budding developers and programmers, such as you folks, and divided the content into 3 categories – Core Java, Advanced Java and Web Java. This developer’s guide focuses on Advanced aspects of the Java platform, and this material has been developed for our exclusive use by Altius Inc. This course covers many important topics such as multi-threading, JDBC, JavaBeans framework, Collections Framework, Advanced Object Oriented Concepts, Java Utility libraries, Lambda expressions and functional programming and many other advanced topics.  This courseware focuses a lot on the hands-on way of learning advanced aspects of Java, and each chapter includes many small projects, on which students can practice and understand the advanced aspects of the Java platform. I am sure that this guide enormously helps the students in absorbing the concepts that will be useful in the professional career. I wish all the students a happy advanced Java learning and   and</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
</resources>
